fabpromocodes.in 2019-04-07

# Privacy policy - fabpromocodes.in

Fabpromocodes, We taking your privacy into consideration are committed to protect it in all respects. With a view to offer the most enhanced and complete internet experience to its users, FABPROMOCODES offers a vast cache of Online Sites and diversified community services. Source of information as collected by FABPROMOCODES is (a) information provided by the users and (b) information automatically tracked while navigation (Information).

### USER INFORMATION

To use certain sites / services on our website, users are required to furnish certain information for the registry that may include but not limited to your name, email address, sex, age, PIN code, credit card or debit card details, medical records and history, sexual orientation, biometric information, password etc., and / or your occupation, interests, and the like. The Information as provided by the users empowers us to advance our site and give you the most accommodating experience.

All compelled information is service dependent and FABPROMOCODES may use the above said information to, Preserve, safeguard, and improvise its services (including advertising services) and for originating new services.

Such information will not be contemplated as delicate if it is freely available and accessible in the public domain or is provided under the Right to Information Act, 2005, any rules made there under or any other law for the time being in force.

For placing an order on or through [www.fabpromocodes.in](http://www.fabpromocodes.in/) the information shall be used to service user requests, and the information shall contain user’s name, mailing address, email and phone number. These facts shall be assembled on the purchase of products/gifts certificates or sign up for email notifications.

We also reserve the first 6 digits and last 4 digits of user card number in a secure and encoded manner. The first 6 digits (also known as the bank Identification number) are used to identify the bank name and country where user card was issued. The first 6 and last 4 digits are collectively utilized for fraud detection and prevention purposes.

The principal justification for collecting information is for order processing, shipping and customer service. For instance, we may reach user to cater an update on order, information regarding the shipping status or to clear up questions related to the order. We also utilize this data to enrich our products, services, website content and navigation.

### COOKIES

To emend the reactivity for our users, we may use “cookies”, or identical electronic devices to gather information to allot each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to appreciate the user’s personal interests using the identified computer. We have no course of learning you unless you deliberately identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no road of knowing who you are, though we allot a cookie to your computer. The only private information a cookie can have is data you provide. A cookie cannot scan the information off your hard disk. Our advertisers may also allow their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a procedure that we do not control. We receive and reserve specific types of data whenever you engage with us via website, application or Service through your computer / laptop / notebook or mobile / tablet / pad / handheld device etc.

### Opting Out

If a user opts out using Ads Settings, the unique DoubleClick cookie ID on the user’s browser is written with the phrase “OPT_OUT”. Since there is no longer a unique cookie ID, the opt-out cookie can’t be confederated with a specific browser.

### Log File Information

We mechanically gather limited data about your computer’s connection to the Internet, mobile number, including your IP address, when you drop in our site, application or service. Your IP address is a number that lets computers affixed to the Internet know where to send you data – such as the pages you view. We spontaneously receive and record data from your browser, incorporating your IP address, your computer’s name, your operating system, browser type and version, CPU speed, and connection speed. We may also gather log data from your device, including your location, IP address, your device’s name, device’s serial number or unique identification number (e.g. UDiD on your iOS device), your device operating system browser type and version, CPU speed, and connection speed etc.

### Information from other Sources:

We may accept information about you from other sources, attach it to out account information and regard it in accordance with this policy. If you give information to the platform provider or other partner, whom we offer services, your account information and order information may be run on to us. We may procure updated contact data from third parties to correct our log file and accomplish the Services or to impart with you.

### Demographic and purchase information:

We may quote other sources of demographic and other information in order to furnish you with more objective communications and promotions. We use Google Analytics, among others, to trace the user conduct on our website. Google Analytics particularly has been licensed to support display advertising towards helping us attain knowledge of our users’ Demographics and Interest. The records are incognito and cannot be joined with any one’s personally identifiable data that you may have parted with us. If you don’t want Analytics to be functioned in your browser, you can install the Google Analytics browser add-on

### LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES / AD-SERVERS

The website or application may contain links to other websites or applications. Such websites or applications are controlled by their respective privacy policies which are outside our control. Once you flee our servers (you can disclose where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any data you provide is controlled by the privacy policy of the operator of the application, you are haunting. That policy may vary from ours. If you can’t discover the privacy policy of any these sites via a link from the application’s homepage, you should approach the application or website owners directly for more information. When we show information to our advertisers – to help them learn our spectators and affirm the value of the advertising on our websites or Applications – it is commonly in the frame of accumulated statistics on traffic to various pages / content within our websites or Applications. We utilize third-party advertising companies to aid ads when you visit our websites or Applications. These companies may use data (not including your name. address, email address or telephone number or any other personally identifiable information) about your visits to this and other websites or application, in order to serve advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We don’t give any personally identifiable information to third aprty websites /  advertisers / ad-servers without your consent.

### INFORMATION SHARING

FABPROMOCODES distributes the sensitive personal data to any third party without obtaining the former permission of the User in the following limited cases:

  1. When it is called for or required by law or by any court or governmental agency or authority to disclose, for the intention of verification of identity or for the prohibition, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or prosecution and punishment of offences. These disclosures are made in good faith and opinion that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these Terms; for obeying with the applicable laws and regulations.
  2. FABPROMOCODES proposes to share such data within its group companies and officers and employees of such group companies for the purpose of processing personal information on its behalf. We also guarantee that these recipients of such data agree to process such information based on our instructions and in obedience with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

### ACCESSING AND UPDATIND PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you use FABPROMOCODES’s websites, we make moral persuasion efforts to supply you, as and when requested by you, with gate to your personal information and shall further assure that any personal data or sensitive personal data or information inexact or inadequate shall be corrected or improvised as possible, open to any demand for such personal data or sensitive personal data or data to be retained by law or for legal business purposes. We request individual users to identify themselves and the data requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may deny to process requests that are extravagantly repetitive or systematic, require unequal technical effort, threatens the privacy of others, or would be highly impractical (for example, requests respecting data lying on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any instance, where we give data access and correction, we provide this service free of charge, except if doing so would desire unequal effort. Due to the way we hold certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take some time before they are deleted from our running servers and may remain in our backup systems.

### INFORMATION SECURITY

We hold relevant security reaches to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or loss of data. These include internal analysis of our data collection, repository and processing practices and security measures to defend from illegitimate access to systems where we reserve personal information.

Data accumulated on FABPROMOCODES is securely reserved within the FABPROMOCODES governed database. The database is reserved on servers secured behind a firewall; entry to the servers is password – guarded and is stringently limited. How active our security measures are, no security system is impermeable. We cannot assure the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that data you provide will not be ambushed while being forwarded to us over the Internet. Any information you incorporate in a posting to the discussion areas is accessible to anyone over Internet.

Any how the internet is highly growing medium. We may change our privacy policy frequently whenever we need to inculcate necessary changes. The use of data we collect will always be steady with policy under which the data was gathered, regardless of what the new policy may be.

We utilize third- party advertising companies to provide ads when you view our website. These companies may use data (not containing your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to serve advertisements about goods and services that interest you. Any accusations or concerns with regards to content or to report any abuse of laws or breach of these terms may be taken up with nominated grievance officer as specified below via post or by sending email to [info@fabpromocodes.in](mailto:info@fabpromocodes.in)
